thebreastcancersite.com 2007-06-07

# Privacy @ The Breast Cancer Site

For questions regarding this privacy statement, please contact [customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com](mailto:customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com). 

GreaterGood Network, owners and operators of The Hunger Site, The Breast Cancer Site, The Child Health Site, The Literacy Site, The Rainforest Site, The Animal Rescue Site, GreaterGood.com and MuseumShop.com has created this privacy statement to spell out our firm commitment to individual privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

GreaterGood Network deeply respects the privacy of its visitors. You are not required to provide any personal information to visit the site and click. Site visitors can voluntarily provide personal information to sign up for an e-Newsletter, our reminder e-mails, or other notifications regarding the site. If you do so, we will use the information you provide only to send you a periodic e-mail. We will not share your personal information with any third party unless you grant us explicit permission in response to a request from us. 

When you purchase something at one of the GreaterGood Network stores, we will never sell your name, cause affiliation, e-mail address, shopping preferences or other personally identifiable information to any third party. For fulfillment purposes, our drop ship vendors (i.e. wreaths, flowers, coffee) are notified of your shipping and e-mail addresses. You may occasionally receive promotional materials from some of these vendors. When you purchase a Gift That Gives More(TM), you may receive communication directly from the charitable partner who fulfills the gift. 

GreaterGood Network uses IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web sites. IP addresses are not linked to anything personally identifiable. 

Each of our websites contains links to other websites, including sponsor websites and other philanthropic websites. GreaterGood Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and encourages you to independently review these companies' privacy policies. 

## Cookies

You do _not_ have to accept cookies in order to click and have your click count! 

For enhanced site visitor experience, we may use a cookie to store your click history. This would only be used to display your click history to you, and is purely optional. In addition, some of our site underwriters may use cookies in the process of displaying their sponsor ads. In any case, you are not required to accept cookies to click. 

## Corrections / Updates

You may contact us at any time regarding privacy concerns. You can also contact us to change or update any information you wish to supply us with: 

  * e-mail us at [customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com](mailto:customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com)
  * write to us at the address below

GreaterGood Network (owner & operator of The Breast Cancer Site) makes every effort to be in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. The following explains the Act and what GreaterGood Network does to meet its requirements. 

## About the Act

If you operate a commercial Web site or an online service directed to children under 13 that collects personal information from children or if you operate a general audience Web site and have actual knowledge that you are collecting personal information from children, you must comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and Rule apply to individually identifiable information about a child that is collected online, such as full name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child. The Act and Rule also cover other types of information -- for example, hobbies, interests and information collected through cookies or other types of tracking mechanisms — when they are tied to individually identifiable information. 

## How GreaterGood Network Complies with the Act

GreaterGood Network does not collect individually identifiable information about children. Registration and subscription services are for persons aged 13 and older only. We request that no child under 13 register on our site. 

If you have questions or concerns about GreaterGood Network's compliance with the Act, please contact us at GreaterGood Network: (206) 859-5201 or e-mail: [customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com](mailto:customerservice@thebreastcancersite.com). 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact:
